When I was in grade school,
I was a gloomy, sullen, unpleasant child.
And because of that,
I didn't have any friends.
Ko-chan?
Your cousin, Carol-chan,
is here to play with you.
She's as pretty as a little angel!
Adults are always so quick to
describe little kids as "angels."
Oh, honey, do you have to be like that?
Hello.
She's...
an actual angel.
When I throw a jab or a straight,
it always lands
But when I'm aiming for your heart,
I miss every time
Parallel, zigzagging, awkward, incoherent
When you look my way and move closer to me
I know it doesn't mean the same thing for you
But I wish we could stay like this forever
My changing feelings are driving me crazy
The moment you turn to face me,
take that! Telepathy
If only we could feel the same thing
I want to kick this pesky subtlety away
I want to know everything,
I want to know everything
I can't fool you forever
I can't keep this hidden
I want to shout out my secret, AHHH
Take that! Telepathy
Te-te-te-telepathy
Telepathy
The Angel's
True Face
"The Angel's True Face."
I-It's good to meet you!
I'm Misaki Kosuke!
I admire your resolve to get stronger.
Thank you!
He said he wanted to join the dojo,
but I didn't think he really would.
But you are clearly...
weak.
You think so, too?!
No, wait.
I see something more behind the weakness.
Wh-What is it?
There's an evil spirit lurking in your soul.
You had best be careful.
Oh...
That's my dad for you.
Senpai, we'll start with running!
Osu!
We're only going up and
down 200 little steps!
Next is strength training.
Three sets of fifty push-ups!
You haven't pushed up once yet!
Senpai, you'll be having a match next!
R-Right now?!
"Train in extremes" is
our motto at this dojo.
Your opponent isn't gonna care
what kind of condition you're in.
Your first opponent...
will be me.
My first battle with Jun-kun...
I want him to face me seriously.
If I can beat you in this fight...
Do you think Aizawa-san will
actually acknowledge me a little?
Who knows?
This is Jun-kun's real strength!
He said Aizawa-san was stronger than him,
but there's no way!
He's overwhelming!
Jun looks like he's having a blast.
Nothing like when he's up against me.
Don't swing your arm out so wide.
And don't think you can get by
on just the heat of the moment.
If you want someone stronger
to acknowledge you,
you gotta cough up the effort, layer upon
bloody layer, until you surpass them.
There's no other way.
I know I can't win,
but if I can at least get one hit in...
Oh, crap.
Where am I?
In my room.
What about practice?
It's already over.
I'm sorry!
Jun really doesn't know how to hold back.
I really am pathetic, aren't I?
Of course not!
Also... were you hoping to get
stronger for Carol's sake?
Wha?!
Well, th-that's, uh...
Yeah.
That's right, actually.
So I was right!
Given the way she is,
she's gotten herself into trouble a
ton of times since we were little.
That's why I wanted to get
stronger for her sake.
But I've never been able
to do anything at all.
Like this last time...
I'm just so...
I told you, Senpai, you're not pathetic!
Just because someone's better
than you at one thing
doesn't make it right to reject
everything about yourself!
You said that yourself!
Besides, no matter how much
you train up your body,
the things you can resolve with this
are things that don't even matter.
There are different kinds of strength.
Ko-chan, you've seemed a
little more manly lately.
What? Really?
Yeah.
I've actually been going to
Aizawa-san's family dojo.
Huh?
Aizawa-san's dad is amazing!
Of course, that also makes
his practices tough...
But I want to become the kind
of man that she'll acknowledge!
Ko-chan...
How do you feel about Tomo-chan?
Huh? Why do you ask that?
Just tell me.
I see Aizawa-san as... well...
a role model, I guess.
It's obvious that she's physically strong,
but she's more than just that.
She's someone I want to catch up to
and be good enough to
stand alongside someday.
Huh...
Jun-kun, Jun-kun.
Want to hang out with me after school?
Huh?
I don't particularly want
to hang out with you, no.
I don't either, particularly.
Then why'd you ask?
I heard you asking Junichiro
to hang out with you today.
What are you planning?
Oh, you saw that, huh?
I don't know what you're up to,
but all of your meddling—
Hey, Misuzu-chan.
Do you still think everything's
going to go your way?
All right! This way!
Wait up!
Why did you want to come to the park?
To watch people playing.
Why would you just watch other people play?
Go play with them.
Tomo and Gundo would join you.
I don't think things will
work like that anymore.
Did something happen?
I said something really mean to
Misuzu-chan at school today,
and I'm doing something mean to Tomo now.
I'm not...
Don't take Tomo for a fool.
I don't know what you did,
but Tomo's not the type to give
up on a friend just like that.
Okay, fine. You've got me for today.
You'll play with me?
Only a little.
Why?
Why did this happen?
Wow, so this is your room, huh?
Just leave now. Please.
Nope.
See, the thing is, there's someone I like,
but it's just not panning out.
What does that have to do with me?
If it doesn't work out,
it's partially your fault.
What? My fault?
Yep.
So I came here to take out
my frustrations on you.
I'm gonna torture you
a little. Don't cry, okay?
Who, me?
Here I go.
Have it your way.
Go home once you get bored.
Mwah.
Wh-What the hell did you—
Slam!
Rawr.
Sh-She's scaring me!
Stop it!
I won't do anything.
Why are you so afraid of girls?
You react like that to
Tomo-chan, too, don't you?
Poor Tomo-chan.
If you keep that up, you won't
get to be with her anymore.
Jun? Weren't you hanging
out with Carol today?
J-Jun?!
Sorry.
I just kinda... got hit with
an attack I wasn't expecting.
What the heck did this to
a guy as tough as you?
That blonde chick was right.
But I still can't fully
accept that Tomo is a girl.
And I bet it's because...
We still haven't settled
that man-to-man score yet.
What's wrong?
I'll help if you need it.
Nah.
It's not something that you can help with.
I mean, we're talking about that—
Hi.
Jun-kun, Tomo-chan, I'm sorry.
Huh? O-Okay...
I'm sorry about yesterday, Misuzu-chan.
It's fine.
But how did Senpai react to the news?
Actually...
I hung out with Jun-kun yesterday.
Just the two of us.
Huh?
We went to the park, and then
we hung out in his room.
R-Really?
Did you have a good time?
Ko-chan made a really weird face.
You're a frightening woman.
There's no telling what you'd
do if left to your own devices.
Maybe I should just get you
together with Senpai already.
You can do that?
You're amazing, Misuzu-chan!
I feel like she's going to
be the bigger problem.
Carol, have you ever let Senpai
see you being serious?
Gundo-san, what did you want to talk about?
How do you feel about Carol?
Huh?!
H-How do I... I mean,
she's like a little sister to—
You can drop that front now.
You love her, don't you?
That's right. I love her.
No kidding.
Your murderous rampage at the
factory made that obvious.
H-Huh?
And you know how she feels, don't you?
Why won't you give her the answer she wants?
B-Because...
Carol is really strong, unlike me.
I've known her forever, but I've
never seen her in a weak state.
I thought I was drawn to her strength,
but once I started thinking about
having that kind of relationship,
I suddenly felt scared.
That whether I said something
to try to woo her
or pushed her away as coldly as I could,
she'd just accept it like it
was the most natural thing.
It's not that I want her to be hurt.
I don't, but...
He does have a point.
Basically, no matter how much time goes by,
she's just so dazzling that
I can't look straight at her.
I really am a sad excuse
for a man, aren't I?
What do you think of couples who keep saying
that they're going to
break up, but never do?
Uh, I don't think it's very—
I thought so.
You wish they'd just disappear, don't you?
No, I wouldn't go that far.
But I think a little bargaining
is necessary sometimes.
She seems to do it on occasion herself.
What? Carol wouldn't do that!
She would, and she is.
You're probably too nice
to pull it off, though,
so would you like me to do it?
Huh? Do what?
You want to see her in a
vulnerable state, don't you?
What? When did we get to that point?
Misuzu-chan, welcome back.
You went to talk to Ko-chan, right?
How did it go?
I'm sure she's going to hate me.
I didn't expect this to weigh on me so much.
But this is the only chance I'll
have to expose her real face.
Frankly, I don't think you have a chance.
Oh, no.
You mean—
You get it, don't you?
You know he doesn't even
think of you as a girl.
I know you used Junichiro
to try to shake him up,
but he probably just felt like a father
giving his daughter away to her groom.
I doubt that will even upset her at all.
Please be at least a little upset...
Liar.
So when they do that, you do this, right?
No, no! You gotta start up higher—
Hey, Carol! It's dangerous
to run in the hall.
Misaki-senpai...
Gundo-san?!
I told her she doesn't
have a chance with you.
What?!
I'm sorry. I didn't think it
would affect her that much.
What are you saying?!
What happened to Carol?!
You need to go to her house right now.
You should at least... at the very least...
see what she looks like right now.
Did Carol go home early because
of something you did?
Tomo...
Yes. It's because I was mean to her.
So what?
You can drop the bad girl act.
Just explain what happened.
Why am I the only one out of the loop?
You're not even going to admonish me?
Hah. Don't take me too lightly.
Um... I heard Carol came
home from school early...
We'll call this one a draw
due to injury, Kosuke-kun.
Come in.
Carol?
She thinks I indirectly rejected her, right?
So will she still greet me with
a smile like she always does?
I'm coming in.
Caro—
I'm an absolute monster.
I couldn't see anything.
No... I never tried to see it.
She's not an angel, and she's not a goddess.
She's just a girl who gets lonely easily.
I'm sorry, Caro—
You jerk! Jerk! Why did you
come here?! Why are you here?!
Carol! Listen to me!
What Gundo-san said was a lie!
It was?
Yes, it was! She said it to try to
get you in a vulnerable state!
Carol?
Gundo!
Misuzu-chan! That jerk! What's her deal?!
It's not like that! I think
she was trying to help me!
Why would Misuzu-chan being
mean to me help you?
Huh?!
Er... well...
Tell me.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Gundo-san made Carol
hate her instead of me.
And look at how much of herself
Carol is showing to me now.
I guess there's no way to run back
to being a coward at this point.
Gundo-san was trying to give me a push,
so I could tell you how I feel.
I love you, Carol.
Sorry it took me so long.
Banzai!
You know what? You know what?
I love you too, Ko-chan!
Thanks! That makes me happy!
What was it that made you like me?
Um... I never thought about it.
You didn't?!
I mean, you've always been by my side,
and you've always been kind to me.
I don't know when or why
it happened anymore.
I love you because I love you.
Ah...
Wait, Carol! What are you doing?!
That'll be all.
Boo.
The reason Carol-chan never stops smiling
is because I told her that she
looks cuter when she smiles.
What?
I said it when she was little to make
her feel better because she was crying,
but she said...
Okay!
And from then on, she wouldn't cry anymore.
I'm scared for her.
As it is, they say love changes a person,
but if you said anything like
that to her as her boyfriend,
there's no telling how it might change her.
It just worries me so much...
Well, I don't have any intention
of saying anything like that.
It'll be okay.
Carol has other important people in her
life now besides me and her family.
She has friends now.
I think she knows what it means
to be loved by those around her.
She wouldn't change just
because of something I said.
That made me trust you a little bit more.
About this much!
Looks like I've got a long road ahead.
Carol's late.
Is she not coming to school today?
I wouldn't blame her.
After what happened yesterday,
even she must be...
Misuzu-chan.
Wh-What?
She's mad! You gotta apologize, Misuzu!
Mwah.
Thank you!
You lost this one, Misuzu!
You lose!
I have not lost.
I swear...
(This suspicious behavior is...)
Hey, you know, I'm all mixed up
It's too complicated, I'm freaking out
I want to look cute to you
(crazy, crazy, drive me crazy, and that's…)
So I'm plotting, bargaining,
sly, and stubborn
Dizzying love
Just tell him to look at you
And watch him stiffen up even more,
because you're both so awkward
What? Even if we're alike in that way
It doesn't make me happy, 'cause it
means our love is going nowhere
Cloudy heart, swirling emotions—
I sense rain coming
So I partly open my umbrella,
then sneakily scoot closer to you
Please notice the curl of my
eyelashes as I keep blinking
And don't say I'm acting weird
All this plotting and bargaining
is my sly plan to look cute to you
Try to solve the riddle of
this soft, dizzying love
(Buzzing, fidgeting)
Listen, I might be a bit
tangled in my own web now
But once you unravel the mystery,
you'll see pure lo-love